unisonplatform.com 2009-03-18

# xat.com Privacy Policy

This policy applies only to information gathered through the Service, including the download and use of Materials through the Service, but not to other off-line transactions with xat, nor to transactions with any third party not owned or controlled by xat. By using the Service you agree to accept the practices and terms set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## Personally Identifiable Information You Provide

You may also be asked to provide personally identifiable information in order to use certain Services and to obtain support from xat. This information may include your name, address, telephone number, credit card number (for paid Services), e-mail address and instant messenger user/screen name, as well as the e-mail addresses, user/screen name and telephone numbers of those to whom you send content. Other Users may also provide us with your e-mail address, user/screen name, or telephone number in order to send you content. If you do not want to provide xat with any personally identifiable information, you should not use the Services that require such information.

## Non-Personally identifiable and Aggregate Information

The non-personally identifiable information that we may gather includes your gender, age, zip code, country or territory of residence, IP address, the type of browser that you use, the type and nature of the content that you upload to the Service and access from the Service, the comments and communication that you enter into the Service, the links and transactions with us and with third-parties that you enter into via the Service, and other aspects of your use of the Service. xat uses this information to improve the Service, conduct research, to analyze your and other User's interest in the areas of the Service, to tailor advertising and content displayed to you and other Users, and to inform our advertisers about the number of Users that have viewed their advertising. To do this we may combine information that we have about you with information that we obtain from business partners or other companies. We may also release aggregate demographic information about User trends to partners and other third parties, including third-party advertisers on the Service. An example of this type of information would be patterns of use of the Service based on zip code or age group. We also retain aggregated log files of requested content in order to report overall product usage to content partners and to evaluate User trends.

## Use and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information

xat does not rent or sell personally identifiable information, such as your name or e-mail address, to advertisers.

xat may use your personally identifiable information:

To deliver you the Service and send you notices related to the Service, your Account and necessary updates. This includes fulfilling your requests for products and services and delivering content to you that is sent by other Users. To deliver your content to other Users (we will share your User name with Users to whom you send content). If you do not want to share this information, you should limit the content that you share and the Users that you share it with.

To e-mail you our newsletter, promotions and special offers from us and our partners. You may remove yourself from this list at any time by replying with unsubscribe in the subject of any e-mail that we send to you. To manage your Account and Account access, provide you with Software and Materials, purchase confirmations, support and customer service and to keep track of support and customer service requests.

To determine the technical capabilities of your device and the appropriate content to deliver to you. xat may disclose personally identifiable information to its partners in order to provide the Service, resolve service problems and correct errors in the Service (including customer inquiries, billing and credit corrections), to communicate with you about the Service, to provide you with advertising and promotional information in connection with the Service, and to enhance your experience on the Service. However, these companies do not have an independent right to share this information. Due to our contractual obligations with these third parties and the need to share personally identifiable information to deliver and support the Service, we cannot provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of sharing personally identifiable information with these third parties.

Your personally identifiable information may be provided to a third party if xat files for bankruptcy, or there is a transfer of the assets or ownership of xat. xat may also disclose personally identifiable information in order to respond to a subpoena, court order or other such request, or to otherwise establish or exercise our rights, or defend against legal claims. xat may also provide such personally identifiable information order to investigate, prevent and take action regarding fraud or misuse of the Service, to comply with law or in response to a law enforcement agency's request, to enforce our Privacy Policy and end user agreements, and to protect the rights, property and safety of the Service, Users and others.

In addition to other Users that you designate, xat, its partners, and each of their contractors and employees may view the content that you upload to the Service in order to provide the Service and otherwise perform the tasks set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## Cookies and Pixel Tags

Cookies and Flash Local Shared Objects are small bits of data that are deposited on a User's hard drive. The Service utilizes Cookies, Flash Local Shared Objects and IP addresses for certain functions. Cookies permit Users to store their password and other User information without having to constantly re-enter this data. Cookies also permit xat and our advertisers to tailor the Service and advertising to your needs. Some of the advertising served through the Service may be supplied by one or more third parties who may also use cookies. In addition, we may also record the pages you visit on our Service through the use of pixel tags (also called "clear gifs" or "beacons").

## Children

xat does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. xat requests that children under the age of 13 not use the Service nor submit any personal information to the Service. Since information regarding children under the age of 13 is not collected, xat does not knowingly use or distribute personal information regarding children under the age of 13. If xat obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to�not having this information used by these companies, click here. 

## Contact, Corrections and Updates

If you have any questions or comments about this policy, please contact info@xat.com.

## Other Websites and Services

xat is not responsible for the privacy policies of websites and services to which the Service links, or of which the Service is a part. If you provide any information to such third parties different rules regarding the collection and use of your personal information may apply. We strongly suggest you review such third party's privacy policies before providing any data to them.

## Security

xat takes appropriate steps to help ensure data privacy and security including through various hardware and software methodologies. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and the Service, and the Service and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Users of the Service do so at their own risk. xat cannot guarantee the security of any information that is disclosed online.

## Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

## Reasonable Efforts

We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our Privacy Policy. We sometimes release beta versions of our products and services, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products and services are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome User feedback on any privacy concerns you may have. In light of the above and because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, and the security risks associated with using the Internet, xat does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. To the extent permissible under law, xat shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy.

## Modifications of the Privacy Policy

xat reserves the rights to modify its Privacy Policy at any time. Such modifications will become effective on the day they are posted. xat encourages you to frequently review the Privacy Policy for any modifications.
